{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"7272/79",
			"answer":"7272/79",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"1157/75",
			"answer":"1157/75",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4148/18",
			"answer":"4148/18",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9154/15",
			"answer":"9154/15",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"9235/45",
			"answer":"9235/45",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3.549/0.91",
			"answer":"3.549/0.91",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"78.96/6.2",
			"answer":"78.96/6.2",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"259.2/2.7",
			"answer":"259.2/2.7",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"30.07/31",
			"answer":"30.07/31",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"0.0946/0.86",
			"answer":"0.0946/0.86",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}